Short-Fu
========
Become a shortcut master through learning and repetition. You can put your own shortcuts and commands.
Short-Fu is a command line app thats works like https://www.shortcutfoo.com.

Alpha 0.1
=========
- Works only with text commands
- You can create your own command list.

Sample:
```
{
	"title": "Command Line - System Basic",
	"data":
	[
		{
			"question": "Show date and time",
			"answer": "date"
		},
		{
			"question": "Display system uptime",
			"answer" : "uptime"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show calendar",
			"answer" : "cal"
		},
		{
			"question": "Display who is logged in",
			"answer" : "w"
		},
		{
			"question": "Display effective user id",
			"answer" : "whoami"
		},

		{
			"question": "Show info about user",
			"answer" : "finger user"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show kernal info",
			"answer" : "uname -a"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show man page for cmd",
			"answer" : "man cmd"
		},
		{
			"question": "Display free disk space",
			"answer" : "df"
		},
		{
			"question": "Display disk usage stats",
			"answer" : "du"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show memory and swap usage",
			"answer" : "free"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show where app location is",
			"answer" : "whereis app"
		},
		{
			"question": "Show which app",
			"answer" : "which app"
		}		
	]
}
```
